Native Environment to help fight the destruction caused by wild fires.

We utilized several sensors and LoRa to monitor and issues warnings/alerts when the air temperature reaches a certain threshold. When choosing our equipment we tried to choose low cost without giving up too much accuracy. 

There are two programs that need to be ran to test this locally. The first is the receiver program followed by the DHT22_PIR_GPS_Version3 program. 






SIUE CS490
Maxamillion Owens
Juan Carlos Sanchez Gonzalez